Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- The Tawfiq Mosque. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1884; 9516; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref342)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Mosques; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Religious Sites; English Writing
- Boys posing beside a sphinx during an excursion to Saqqara. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1951; 9517; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref343)
  Boys; Students; Saqqara, Egypt; Weapons; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Palm Trees; Photographic Prints; Guns; Hats; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Schools/Education
- A man with a little boy in front of Villa Maraghi. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; 9518; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref344)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Boys; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Houses; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Helwan Public Hospital, previously known as Fouad I Sanitarium. And previously Al Hyatt Hotel. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1926; 9519; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref345)
  Hotels; Photographic Prints; Hospitals; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Nurses; Architecture; Buildings; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums; Arabic Writing
- Group portrait of priests. 29.7 x 39.7 cm, 1948; 9520; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref346)
  Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Saint George Church. Previously known as the German Church. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1871; 9521; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref347)
  Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Religious Sites
- Holy Family Church. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1888; 9522; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref348)
  Architecture; Photographic Prints; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Religious Sites
- Villa no. 26 on AbdelRahman Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; 9523; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref349)
  Buildings; Houses; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Villa no. 36 on Mahmud Khater Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; 9524; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref350)
  Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Palm Trees
- House no. 37 AbdelRahman street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; 9525; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref351)
  Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints
- Entrance of house no. 23 on Mohammed Sayed Ahmed Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; 9526; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref352)
  Buildings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Doors/Entrances; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- Villa no. 10 on Ibrahim Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; 9527; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref353)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Doors/Entrances
- Villa of Mahmoud Khater. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; 9528; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref354)
  Italian Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Street Lamps; Buildings
- Villa on Latif Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated; 9529; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref355)
  Houses; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Saint Barsoum El Erian Monastery in El-Maassara. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; 9530; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref356)
  Landscapes; Architecture; Monasteries/Convents; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Crosses; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing
- Cars in front of Princess Khadija's villa. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated; 9531; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref357)
  Architecture; Regional/National Dress; Royalty; Helwan, Egypt; Palm Trees; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Cars/Trucks; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Transportation
- Jewish Synagogue in Helwan, Egypt. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984; 9532; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref358)
  Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Jewish Religion; Synagogues; Religious Sites
- View from South East Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; 9533; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref359)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Houses; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Landscapes
- View from North Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; 9534; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref360)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Houses; Architecture; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- A view of Helwan from the North. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; 9535; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref361)
  Buildings; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Houses
- A view of Helwan's train station. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910; 9536; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref362)
  Buildings; Landscapes; Architecture; Railways; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- The College de la Sainte Famille boys' school. 19.5 x 30 cm, 1979; 9537; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref363)
  Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Buses; Italian Writing; Architecture; Schools/Education; Transportation
- The College de la Sainte Famille boys' school. 30.5 x 24 cm, 1986; 9538; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref364)
  Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Schools/Education
- The metro station at Helwan. 19.7 x 29.5 cm, 1910; 9539; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref365)
  Buildings; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Trains; Transportation; Railways
- A man shaking a boy's hand. 25.3 x 19.9 cm, Undated; 9540; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref366)
  Teachers; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A group photo of Boy Scouts with their Scout Leaders. 18.3 x 30 cm, 1980/81; 9541; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref367)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Boys; Scouts; Flags; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Tents; Men
- Students in the College de la Sainte Famille playground. 24 x 26.5 cm, Circa 1980-1984; 9542; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref368)
  Architecture; Boys; Students; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Group photo of students with a priest. 20.2 x 29.2 cm, 1985; 9543; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref369)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Students; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair
- Students in the College de la Sainte Famille courtyard. 23.8 x 30 cm, 1982; 9544; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref370)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Boys; Children; Buildings
- Two men wearing traditional Upper Egyptian galabeyas. 21.6 x 26.4 cm, 1984; 9545; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref371)
  Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Regional/National Dress; Men; Turbans; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Regional/National Dress
- Waxworks of Nefertiti and Tutankhamun at the Helwan Wax Museum. 20.2 x 25.4 cm, 1936; 9546; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref372)
  Color Photography; Museums; Statues/Sculptures; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Construction workers at the side of the school building. 12.8 x 26.3 cm, 1984; 9547; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref373)
  Buildings; Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Construction; Workers; Architecture
- School photo of students with their teacher and two priests. 17.7 x 23.2 cm, 1960/61; 9548; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref374)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Students; Schools/Education; Men; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Entrance of a villa at No. 32 Ragheb Street. 24.2 x 18.1 cm, 1984; 9549; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref375)
  Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Photographic Prints
- House on AbdelRahman Street. 18.1 x 24.1 cm, 1984; 9550; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref376)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Graffiti; Italian Writing; Buildings; Doors/Entrances
- House at no. 6 Sobhi Street with clothes drying on a laundry rope on a balcony. 24.2 x 18 cm, 1984; 9551; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref377)
  Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing
- The spire of the Holy Family Church. 23.9 x 18.1 cm, 1984; 9552; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref378)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Churches
- Students in a marching band. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, 1952; 9626; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref379)
  Flags; Marching Band; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Buildings; Boys; Musical Instruments; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Students
- Funeral of Father Giacomelli. 16.5 x 24 cm, November 1924; 9627; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref380)
  Parades/Processions; Hats; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Photographic Prints; Umbrellas/Parasols; Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Students; Priests/Clergymen; Arabic Writing; Funeral Proceedings; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt
- Group photo of students with their teachers during a field trip. 17.9 x 23.5 cm, Circa 1930; 9628; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref381)
  Animals; Uniforms; Hats; Camels; Men; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Fezes/Tarbouches; Facial Hair
- Class photo. 17 x 23.7 cm, 1956/57; 9629; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref382)
  Men; Group Portraits; Students; Boys; Schools/Education; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School photo. 16.8 x 23.8 cm, 1956/57; 9631; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref384)
  Children; Regional/National Dress; Boys; Men; Teachers; Students; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School photo. 17.5 x 23.3 cm, 1956-58; 9632; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref385)
  Schools/Education; Children; Group Portraits; Boys; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Men; Teachers; Students; Facial Hair
- School photo. 17.9 x 23.8 cm, 1958/59; 9633; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref386)
  Students; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Photographic Prints; Boys; Men; Uniforms; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- School photo. 17.5 x 23.2 cm, 1956/57; 9634; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref387)
  Children; Students; Boys; Women; Uniforms; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- First Prep B class photo. 20.2 x 25 cm, 1999/2000; 9635; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref388)
  Women; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Children; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Uniforms; Color Photography; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School photo of teachers and priests. 17.4 x 23.2 cm, 1989/90; 9636; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref389)
  Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Women; Teachers; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School photo. 20.2 x 24.3 cm, 1999/2000; 9637; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref390)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Women; Boys; Children; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- School photo. 20.2 x 24.3 cm, 1989/90; 9638; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref391)
  Arabic Writing; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Men; Women; Schools/Education; Teachers; Students; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School photo. 20.2 x 2.2 cm, 1999/2000; 9639; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref392)
  Women; Boys; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Children; Uniforms; Men; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- School photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999/2000; 9640; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref393)
  Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Women; Men; Children; Teachers; Students; Boys; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- School photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999/2000; 9641; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref394)
  Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Men; Women; Teachers; Color Photography; Students; Uniforms; Boys; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A man giving a speech during a ceremony. 20.2 x 25.6 cm, 1985; 9642; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref395)
  Carpets/Rugs; Microphones; Schools/Education; Ceremonies; Women; Men; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Awards; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- East side view of Helwan. 20.2 x 21.2 cm, 1984; 9643; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref396)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Palm Trees; Landscapes; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Color Photography
- Class photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999/2000; 9644; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref397)
  Children; Color Photography; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Teachers; Students; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- View of school from above. 20.2 x 24.6 cm, 15 September 1991; 9645; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref398)
  Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt
- Class photo. 17.7 x 23.9 cm, 1978; 9646; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref399)
  Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Uniforms; Women; Color Photography; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Group photo with the eldest priest in College de la Sainte Famille. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9647; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref400)
  Men; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair
- Students in front of Helwan metro station. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9648; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref401)
  Helwan, Egypt; Children; Railways; Color Photography; Boys; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Uniforms; Men; Architecture; Buses; Students; Photographic Prints; Transportation; Parades/Processions
- A teacher handing a souvenir to the graduates pioneer. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9649; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref402)
  Group Portraits; Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Ceremonies; Men; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Awards
- School choir and band during an event. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9650; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref403)
  Singing; Helwan, Egypt; Choirs; Color Photography; Students; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Teachers; Children; Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Girls; Musical Instruments; Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School alumni event. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9651; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref404)
  Group Portraits; Students; Men; Arabic Writing; Women; Awards; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- School alumni at a school event. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9652; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref405)
  Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Boy scouts in a marching band. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9653; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref406)
  Scouts; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Transportation; Arabic Writing; Men; Buses; Children; Color Photography; Uniforms; Flags; Marching Band; Boys; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Parades/Processions
- School's 100-year celebration march. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9654; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref407)
  Events/Occasions; Arabic Writing; Banks; Outdoors; Architecture; Uniforms; Boys; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Parades/Processions; Children
- Police music band celebrating school's 100-year celebration at the police station. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9655; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref408)
  Police; Ceremonies; Schools/Education; Woodwind Instruments; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Marching Band; Musicians; Color Photography; Musical Instruments; Arabic Writing; Boys; Men; Uniforms; Cameras
- A teacher welcoming a police officer/alumni. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9656; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref409)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Arabic Writing; Students; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Men; Photographic Prints; Museums; Helwan, Egypt
- School representatives. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9657; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref410)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Facial Hair
- Group photo of nuns and priests at the school's 100 years celebration. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988; 9658; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref411)
  Religious Crosses; Color Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Arabic Writing; Carpets/Rugs; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A priest receiving a gift from a Vatican representative beside a sheikh. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1978; 9659; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref412)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Sheikhs; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Christian-Muslim relations; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Events/Occasions; Turbans; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- School principal along with a Vatican representative and two teachers. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1979; 9660; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref413)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Girls; Women; Color Photography; Food; Events/Occasions; Children; Schools/Education
- Priest shaking hands with a priest beside the Vatican ambassador. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1979; 9661; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref414)
  Sheikhs; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Men; Christian-Muslim relations; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- A teacher receiving a gift from the Vatican ambassador. 8.9 x 12.5 cm, 1978; 9662; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref415)
  Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Boys holding trophies during the school's 100-year celebration. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1978; 9663; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref416)
  Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Boys; Students; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Awards
- A teacher leading the school music band. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1983; 9664; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref417)
  Helwan, Egypt; Events/Occasions; Color Photography; Children; Uniforms; Boys; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Students; Musicians; Musical Instruments; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Men
- Guests during Flag Day. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1984; 9665; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref418)
  Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Priests/Clergymen; Flags; Events/Occasions; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Crosses; Canes/Walking Sticks; Facial Hair
- Student receiving cup of excellence on Flag Day. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1984; 9666; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref419)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Group Portraits; Boys; Ceremonies; Students; Flags; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Awards; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A teacher welcoming the school principal and head manager on Flag Day. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1984; 9667; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref420)
  Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Men; Events/Occasions; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Student receiving an award from the Deputy Commissioner. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, 1985; 9668; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref421)
  Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Medals/Insignia; Arabic Writing; Men; Awards